Guide to the Northup & O'Brien Architectural Records
Northup & O'Brien Architectural Records
- Specifications, 31 linear feet
  - Classroom Building - Change Orders; Winston-Salem Teachers' College, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Office Building for Lashmit; James, Brown, and Pollock, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Caldwell County Library, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Caldwell County Library - Change Orders, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Pilot Plant; R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Pilot Plant - Change Orders; R. J. Reynolds Tobacco Company, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Sunday School Building - First Christian Church; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Sunday School Building - First Christian Church; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Public Library; Thomasville, N.C., undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Public Library; Thomasville, N.C., undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - School for Handicapped, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - School for Handicapped, Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Rondthaler Memorial Building and Home Moravian Church, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Gymnasium Addition, Salem College, undated (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Post Office; Davidson, N.C., undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Public Works Facility - Naval Seaplane Facility; Hertford, N.C., undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Aircraft Parking Areas, Seaplane Ramps and Bulkheads; Seaplane Facility, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Boat House and Operations Building; Naval Air Station, undated (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Fraternity House; Davidson College, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Sanctuary, Waughtown Baptist Church, undated (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - City National Bank; Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Air Conditioning; Winston-Salem City Hall, undated (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Air Conditioning; Piedmont Publishing Company, undated (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Mount Tabor School, Forsyth County, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Mount Tabor School - Change Orders, Forsyth County, undated (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Underground Utilities; Winston-Salem Teachers' College, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Store Front Remodeling; West End Properties, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Parking Deck; Raleigh, N.C., undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Power Plant and Shop; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Power Plant and Shop Building; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Cook's Warehouse Addition, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Amos and Smith Hosiery Company; Mill Addition, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Wesley B. Speas School; Addition, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Wesley B. Speas School; Addition, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Administration Building; Naval Air Station, Harvey Point, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Howard Johnson's Motor Lodge, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Wiley Jr. High School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Wiley Jr. High School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Wiley Jr. High School and Hanes Park - Contracts; Hanes Park Elementary, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Hanes Park Elementary School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Hanes Park Elementary School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Konnoak and Ardome Jr. High Schools, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Konnoak and Ardome Jr. High Schools, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Knollwood Baptist Church; Education Building, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Knollwood Baptist Church; Education Building, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Goodwill Rehab. Center; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Goodwill Rehab. Center; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Dormitory; Davidson College, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Classroom and Administration Building; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Classroom and Administration Building; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - First Federal Savings and Loan; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - First Christian Church; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Waughtown Jr. High; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Waughtown Jr. High; Winston-Salem - Change Orders, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Science Building; Salem College, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Douglas Rights Memorial Chapel; Trinity Moravian Church, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Hanes Building; Research Triangle Institute, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Hanes Building; Research Triangle Institute, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Hanes Building; Research Triangle Institute, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Cafeteria and Student Union; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Cafeteria and Student Union; N.C. Wesleyan College - Change Orders and Contacts, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Men's Dorm; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Men's Dorm; N.C. Wesleyan College - Change Orders, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Women's Dorm; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Women's Dorm; N.C. Wesleyan College - Change Orders, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Addendum No. 1-4; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Northwest High School Addition; Forsyth County, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Northwest High School Addition; Forsyth County, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Annex to Prof. Building; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Annex to Prof. Building; Winston-Salem - Change Orders and Contracts, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Centenary Methodist Church, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Fine Arts Bldg.; Davidson College, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Fine Arts Bldg.; Davidson College, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Kimberly Park Terrace; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Ext. Underground Utilities; Winston-Salem Teachers College, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Northwest High School; Cafeteria, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Northwest High School; Cafeteria, undated (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Gym and Swimming Pool; NC Wesleyan College, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Forsyth General Hospital, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Forsyth General Hospital; General Specs. I, undated (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Forsyth General Hospital; General Specs. I, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Forsyth General Hospital; General Specs. II, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Forsyth General Hospital; Mechanical Specs., undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Forsyth General Hospital; Electrical Specs., undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Forsyth General Hospital; Addendum File, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Revisions on Laundry; Forsyth General Hospital, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - East Winston Jr. High, undated (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - East Winston Jr. High, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Sherwood Forest Elementary; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Field Lighting; Paisley Jr. High, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Girls Dorm; Winston-Salem Teachers College, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Central Office Building Addition; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Thruway Shopping Center Store; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - St. Paul's Episcopal Church; Kitchen Renovation, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Dining Hall; Winston-Salem Teachers' College, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Woolworth Alterations; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - North Senior High School; Forsyth County, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Heating and Air Conditioning; St. Paul's Episcopal Church, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Nurses' Residence; Forsyth Memorial Hospital; General Specs., undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Nurses' Residence; Forsyth Memorial Hospital; Mechanical and Electrical Specs. - Addendum, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Sanctuary; New Philadelphia Moravian Church, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Men's Dorm; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Women's Dorm; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Addendum File; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Infirmary; N.C. Wesleyan College, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Reynolds Auditorium; Renovations; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Reynolds Auditorium; Renovations - Electrical, etc; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Pegram Hall Renovation; Winston-Salem Teachers' College, undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Student Union Alterations; Davidson College, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Messiah Moravian Church; Alterations and Additions, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Messiah Moravian Church; Alterations and Additions, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Goodwill Rehab. Center; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Goodwill Rehab. Center; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Goodwill Rehab. Center; Hot Water Heating and Addendum File, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Service Building; Salem College, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Fine Arts Center; Salem College, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Fine Arts Center - Salem College; Addendum File and Water, Steam, Elec., undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Old Salem Reception Center, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - College Union - Phase II; Davidson College, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Reynolda Manor Branch Library; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - City Hall Fallout Shelter; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Long Term Care Unit (John C. Whitaker Care Unit); Forsyth Memorial Hospital, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Reynolds Memorial Hospital; General Volume 1, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Reynolds Memorial Hospital; General Volume 2, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Reynolds Memorial Hospital; Mechanical and Electrical, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Reynolds Memorial Hospital; Addendum File, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Sedge Garden Methodist; Kernersville, N.C., undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Thruway Shopping Center; Thalimers Store, undated (Box 44, Folder 63-09.1)
  - Thruway Shopping Center; Site Work, undated (Box 44, Folder 63-09a.1)
  - Thruway Shopping Center; Thruway Stores, undated (Box 44, Folder 63-09b.2)
  - Thruway Shopping Center; Wilson\Peasants Addendum, undated (Box 44, Folder 63-09d.2)
  - Science Building; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 44, Folder 63-10.1)
  - R. J. Reynolds High; New Boilers, undated (Box 44, Folder 63-11.1)
  - Mausoleum; Salem Cemetery, undated (Box 44, Folder 63-12.2)
  - Library, Winston-Salem College, undated (Box 44, Folder 63-13.1)
  - South Hall; Salem College, undated (Box 44, Folder 63-14.1)
  - Bethlehem Community College; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 44, Folder 64-01.2)
  - Old Chapel, Salem College, undated (Box 44, Folder 64-02.1)
  - Dormitory, Salem College, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Church School, Children's Home, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Old Salem Hatters Shop (No Specs), undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Baby Cottage (No Specs), undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Library and Gym Classroom; NC Wesleyan College, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Library and Gym Classroom; NC Wesleyan College, undated (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - South Forsyth High School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - South Forsyth High School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Old Salem Inc., Electric Util. (No Specs), undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Steam Plant; Davidson College (No Specs), undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Krispy Kreme Office - Altercations and Additions; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Office Building; Salem Steel Company, undated (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - No specs. (64-14 -> see 64-07), undated (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Boys and Girls Dorms; N.C. School of the Arts, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Boys and Girls Dorms; N.C. School of the Arts, undated (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Utilities and Bolier Plant, Dormitories; NC School of the Arts, undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - No specs., undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Elevator to Dining Hall; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Classroom Building Alt.; N.C. School of the Arts, undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - North Forsyth High School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - North Forsyth High School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Chambers Auditorium Add.; Davidson College, undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - w. Suburban Jr. Sr. High School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - w. Suburban Jr. Sr. High School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - No specs., undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Roof and Gutters; R. J. Reynolds High School, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - No specs. - Womble, Carlyle, Sandridge, and Rice, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Knollwood Baptist Church, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Knollwood Baptist Church, Winston-Salem, undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - No Specs.; Goodwill Addition, undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Eller Hall Renovations; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Eller Hall Renovations; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Classroom Building; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Classroom Building; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - No specs., undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Religious Education Building; St. Anne's Episcopal Church, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - No Specs., undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - No specs., undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Piedmont Park Housing; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Goodwill Rehab. Alterations, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - New Parking; Thruway Shopping Center, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Admin. Building Alterations; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Admin. Building Alterations; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Salem Academy Additions; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - No specs., undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Thomas Jefferson Jr. High; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Thomas Jefferson Jr. High; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - No specs., undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Science Building Alt.; Winston-Salem College, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Town Steak House; Walkway and Canopy; Thruway Shopping Center, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Site Work; Thomas Jefferson Jr. High; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - No specs., undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Bickett Hall Renovation; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - High Rise Apartments for Elderly; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - High Rise Apartments for Elderly; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - High Rise Apartments for Elderly; Winston-Salem State College, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Central Office Building; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Central Office Building; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - No specs., undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Thalhimers Store Additions; Thruway Shopping Center, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - No specs., undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Day Care Centers at Housing Projects; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Day Care Centers at Housing Projects; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - No specs., undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Moravian Home; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Moravian Home; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - No specs., undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Medical Park Hospital; General Construction, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Medical Park Hospital; Mechanical and Electrical, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Medical Park Hospital, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - No specs., undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Student Union; Winston-Salem University, undated (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Student Union; Winston-Salem University, undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - No specs., undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Library Addition, Winston-Salem University, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Library Addition; Winston-Salem University, undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - No specs., undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Site Work; Medical Park Hopsital; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - No specs., undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Piedmont Aviation; Reservation Center, undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Piedmont Aviation; Reservation Center, undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - No specs., undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Rehab. Center; Forsyth Memorial Hospital, undated (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Rehab. Center; Forsyth Memorial Hospital, undated (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - No specs., undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Carolina Hall Renovation; Winston-Salem State University, undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Carolina Hall Renovation; Winston-Salem State University, undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Commissioned Officers Club; Cherry Point, undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - John C. Whitaker; Regional Reahb. Center; Forsyth Memorial Hospital, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Regional Reahb. Center; Forsyth Memorial Hospital, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Addition to Winn-Dixie; Thruway Shopping Center, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Day Care Center; Winston-State Housing Authority, undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Richmond HIll Law School; East Bend, N.C., undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - C. E. Pleasants, Jr. Residence; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - NCNB Bldg.; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - NCNB Parking Deck; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Winston-Salem Savings and Loan; Winston-Salem, N.C., undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - NCNB Walks and Plaza; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Addition to Gym; Kernersville Jr. High, undated (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Kernersville Elementary; Addition, undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Library; Salem College, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Cherry-Marshall Parking Deck; Volume 1, undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Cherry-Marshall Parking Deck; Volume 2, undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Dellabrook Presbyterian & No Specs., undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Moravian House; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - N.C. School of the Arts; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - N.C. School of the Arts - Campus Fire Protection, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - N.C. School of the Arts; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Classroom Rewiring, undated (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - No specs., undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Summit School; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - High Point - Guilford Co.; Solid Waste Disposal Facility, undated (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - N.C. School of the Arts; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Forsyth Bank & Trust Co.; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Scale Station; Solid Waste Disposal Facility; High Point - Guilford Co., undated (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art (The Gallery of Contemporary Art), undated (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art (The Gallery of Contemporary Art), undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Ice Hockey Rink; Memorial Coliseum; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Trinity Moravian Church; Additions and Renovations, undated (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Health and P. E. Building - Additions and Renovations; Winston-Salem State University, undated (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Aycock Aud. Renovation; UNCG, undated (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Workspace; N.C. School of the Arts, undated (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Cottage No. 1 Alt.; Horizon Residential Care Center, undated (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Walkertown Junior High, undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Eastern Elem. School Addition; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Kernersville Jr. High; Addition, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Medical Park Hospital Add.; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Residence; Mr. and Mrs. T. W. Backfield, Jr., undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Residence; Mr. and Mrs. Nelson T. Grace, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Residence; Mr. and Mrs. Robert Ward, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Richmond Hill Law School; Restoration - Phase I, Part II, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Richmond Hill Law School; Restoration - Phase II & IV, undated (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Hawthorne Rd. Parking Deck for Queensland Parking Co., undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Knollwood Baptist Church Add.; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Augsburg Lutheran Church; Renovation, undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Augsburg Lutheran Church; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Carver HIgh School; Addition/Remodeling, undated (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Latham Elementary School, undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Konnoak Elem. School - Addition/Remodeling, undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Refurbishing War Memorial Aud. - Phase 1, undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Refurbishing War Memorial Aud. - Phase 2, undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Refurbishing War Memorial Aud. - Sound System - Phase 2, undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Director's House - Add. and Renov.; Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art, undated (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Addition and Renovation; Davie Co. Health Center, undated (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Housing Authority of Winston-Salem; Modernization of Projects; NC 12-1, 12-2, 12-4, 12-5, 12-7, undated (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Site Analysis Programming; Forsyth Co. Mental Health; Facility and Workshop, undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Forsyth Co. Mental Health; Facility and Sheltered Workshop, undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Triad United Methodist Home; General Construction, undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Paul Fulton, Jr.; Residence - Renov. and Add., undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Aycock Auditorium Renov.; UNC-G, undated (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Duplex Apt. Complex; Phase 1 - Hayes Home Site; NC Baptist Homes, Inc., undated (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - WORKPLACE; Core Teaching Facility; NCS of the Arts, undated (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Drs. Hugo & Antonia Tettamanti; Residence - Add. and Alt., undated (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - South Fork Elementary; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Cleveland Ave.; Day Care Center, undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Thatcher L. Townsend; Residence, undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Hayes Home, Addition and Renovation, undated (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Hayes Home, Addition and Renovation, undated (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Children's Bldg. - Renov.; Centenary United Meth. Church, undated (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Sedge Garden Elementary; Winston-Salem, undated (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Medical Bldg. - Dr. J. G. Burke; Mt. Airy, N.C., undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Sunrise & Crystal Towers; Winston-Salem Housing Authority, undated (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Feasibility Study; Carolina Theater, undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Feasibility Study; Greensboro Coliseum Complex, undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Feasibility Study; Forsyth County Courthouse Renov., undated (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Financial Material, 1917-1956; 1917 1956; 3 linear feet
  This series consists principally of volumes of financial records--accounts receivable journals, account books, estimate books, and personnel ledgers, 1917-1956. The accounts receivable journals list architectural projects alphabetically, and provide debit and credit figures indicating material and labor costs for each. Detailed in the account books is such information as wages, expenses, and income. The estimate books record the cost estimates for jobs commissioned by the firm. The daybooks record mainly wages and income taxes. Also included in this series is a folder of miscellaneous material taken from several of the financial volumes, including expense statements and some correspondence, 1935-1948.
  - Accounts Receivable Journal, 1917-1937 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Accounts Receivable Journal, 1920-1936 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Accounts Receivable Journal, 1934-1941 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Accounts Receivable Journal, 1938-1947 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Account Book, 1924-1925 (Box 63, Folder 5)